let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "As it ___ dark we ___ to go home",
        answer: "was getting / decided",
        options: [
            "will be getting / had decided",
            "was getting / decided",
            "had got / have decided",
            "would get / shall decide"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 2,
        question: "He ___ looking at her, wondering where he ___ her",
        answer :"kept / had seen",
        options: [
            "kept / had seen",
            "had kept / had seen",
            "being kept / would see",
            "keeps / saw"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 3,
        question: "He said that he ___ school and he ___ to enter the academy",
        answer: "had finished / was going",
        options: [
            "had finished / was going",
            "has finished / is going",
            "finishes / are going",
            "finished / was going"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 4,
        question: "He ___ at the blackboard and ___ that the English teacher ___ the word “apple” there.",
        answer: "looked / saw / was writing",
        options: [
            "has looked / has seen / is writing",
            "is looking / saw / writes",
            "looked / saw / was writing",
            "was looking / sees/wrote"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 5,
        question: "He ___ he ___ lunch an hour before.",
        answer: "said / had had",
        options: [
            "said / had",
            "say / had",
            "says / shall have",
            "said / had had"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 6,
        question: "Ronald Reagan ___ president for 8 years before he ___ .",
        answer: "had been / retired",
        options: [
            "had been / had retired",
            "had been / retired",
            "was / had retired",
            "had been / has retired"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 7,
        question: "I usually ___ there by train but this week-end I ___ by bus",
        answer: "go / am going",
        options: [
            "go / am going",
            "go / was going",
            "go / are going",
            "go / go"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 8,
        question: " Please, ___ me the newspaper the postman ___ today",
        answer: "show / has brought",
        options: [
            "showed / brought",
            "show / brought",
            "shows / brings",
            "show / has brought"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 9,
        question: "I ___ about it at the moment and I think that I ___ how to use it now",
        answer: "am reading / know",
        options: [
            "read / knew",
            "was reading / knew",
            "am reading / know",
            "shall read / have known"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 10,
        question: " It is going to rain. I ___ glad I ___ my umbrella with me today.",
        answer: "am/have taken",
        options: [
            "are/took",
            "am/have taken",
            "am/takes",
            "is/takes"
        ]
    },
]